<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HUB</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="about_this_app">About this app</string>

    <string name="visit_website">Visit website</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="about_hub">Hamdard University Bangladesh is the culmination of the vision and brainchild of Dr. Hakim Mohammad Yousuf Harun Bhuiyan. It was his long cherished vision to set up a “City of Science, Education and Culture” and Hamdard University Bangladesh.Dr. Hakim Mohammad Yousuf Harun Bhuiyan, the architect of Hamdard University Bangladesh, is also the pioneer of modern Hamdard Bangladesh, Managing Director of Hamdard Laboratories (Waqf) Bangladesh and Secretary General of Hamdard Foundation Bangladesh.\n\n Hamdard stands for happiness of all. In the tradition of Hamdard, the community of scholars at the University is committed to the pursuit of truth, academic excellence and advancement of knowledge. The mission of the University is to provide value-based education to all students in its constituent institutions. The doors of the University are open to members of every caste, color and creed; the culture of the University welcomes and respects those whose lives are formed by different traditions and customs recognizing their important contribution to a pluralistic society and to an atmosphere of open discussion essential for sharpening higher faculties of mind. As a community, the University encourages brotherhood, shared decision-making and ecademic freedom.\n\nEducation at the University is holistic and offers opportunities for intellectual, spiritual, emotional, social, cultural and physical upliftment. Student are encouraged to develop knowledge, norms, values and skills which will enrich their lives and prepare them to provide service to national and international communities.</string>

    <string name="about_hfb">Hamdard Foundation Bangladesh was founded by Dr. Hakim Mohammad Yousuf Harun Bhuiyan in 1989 with the recommendation from Shaheed Hakim Mohammed Said and the consent from the Board of Trustees of Hamdard Laboratories (Waqf) Bangladesh. This foundation is run by the earnings of Hamdard Laboratories (Waqf) Bangladesh. The foundation, being a charitable organization, promotes welfare by performing humanitarian affairs and carrying out its charitable, educational and philanthropic activities. Hamdard Foundation Bangladesh promotes and brings about advancement of learning, education and application of knowledge. Poor but brilliant students are granted educational aid or stipends from the Foundation. A Unani Medical College at Bogra, a Unani Medical College at Dhaka and Hamdard Public College at Dhaka have been established and functioning under the financial patronage of this Foundation. The next educational goal of the Foundation is Hamdard University Bangaldesh.\n\nIt gives us immense pleasure to acknowledge that to establish the University, Hamdard has received a great support and cooperation from the University Grants Commission (UGC) Bangladesh, Ministries of Education and Religious affairs of Bangladesh, Waqf administration, Prime Minister’s Secretarial and many others. Hamdard family thankfully recognizes the contribution, help and support of all the members of the Board of trustees of Hamdard Laboratories (Waqf) Bangladesh, the Executive Committee of Hamdard Foundation Bangladesh, the Board of Trustees of Hamdard University Bangladesh and all the Directors and employees of Hamdard Laboratories (Waqf) Bangladesh.\n\nHamdard University Bangladesh is determined to provide quality and time oriented education to the students so that they can fulfill their cherished goals and work hard utmost dedication, morality and sincerity in order to materialize in building a happy and prosperous Bangladesh.</string>

    <string name="about_obj">The objective of Hamdard University Bangladesh will be as follows:\n\n• To provide a specialized and high quality education as preparation for study or future employment in the positions of responsibility across a worldwide range of Health Sciences, Science, Engineering, Arts, Social Sciences, Environmental Science, Development Studies, Computer Science and Information Technology, Business Administration, Travel Tourism and Hospitality Management, Law and Legal Affairs and other profession.\n• To establish and run the university is to provide world class standard education in Bangladesh and develop our graduates up to International Standard through getting accreditation of internationally recognised accreditation bodies.\n•	 To use traditional and modern instructional techniques and technology to the best advantage so as to enhance and enrich students achievements of their educational goals and to culminate their career goals as well as socio-economic development of the country.\n• To establish collaborative and credit transfer programmes with reputed universities to facilitate quality education.</string>

    <string name="about_aims">Hamdrad University Bangladesh aim is to promote and create a learning environment to establish an Educational and Cultural hub in Bangladesh as well as in Asia-pacific, where Teachers, Students and Scholars will have world class Education, Learning and Research facilities.\n\nTo make sure that our innovative, quality programs are relevant to the realities of the world today and to your dreams and goals, we invite you to actively participate in designing your individual programme. </string>

    <string name="about_founder_message">Hamdard University Bangladesh has been established and functioning under the financial patronage of Hamdard Foundation, a charitable organization that promotes welfare by performing humanitarian affairs, charitable, educational and philanthropic activities. This Foundation is run by the earnings of Hamdard Laboratories (Waqf) Bangladesh.\n\nThe primary goal of the University is to achieve a level of academic excellence which measures favourably on the touchstone of international standards. The University will endeavour in building up resources, necessary for an institution of higher education devoted to teaching and research.\n\nEducation at Hamdard University addresses to the fullest development of a person intellectually, spiritually, physically, socially and culturally. The University will promote these goals by providing adequate opportunities, suitable facilities and appropriate support services for the comprehensive growth of all the students, faculty and staff alike.\n\nTo provide state-of-the-art educational and research facilities, about 100 bighas of land has been procured and developed at Gazaria, Munshiganj, in the estuary of the mighty river Meghna and meek Phuldi. An ideal permanent campus for this University would be in a large and wide open space away from the crowded city in proximity to the nature. The area of the permanent campus is larger than any other existing private universities in Bangladesh.\n\nI am grateful to all the members of the Board of Trustees, the University Management and those who have contributed immensely in establishing Hamdard University Bangladesh.\n\nDr. Hakim Md. Yousuf Harun Bhuiyan\nSecretary General, Board of Trustees, Hamdard University Bangladesh and\nManaging Director, Hamdard Laboratories (waqf) Bangladesh</string>

    <string name="vision">The vision of Hamdard University Bangladesh is to foster national development process through the establishment of an excellent institution of higher education which is responsive to society´s need,able to develop creative leaders and actively contribute to learning and enriching knowledge.</string>


    <string name="library">The University library covers an area of 1,600 square feet on the ground floor of the first building. The library has a collection of over 10,000 textbooks, journals, magazines, research papers and other digital resources. In addition, the Library has a subscription to the journal archive. Professional library staff perform literature searches, offer training, referral and bibliographic services. E-mail and Internet browsing facilities for students and photocopying are available. The online book catalog is available through the Internet. It has a few workstations and is going to install a few more for the users. It also has a newspaper corner, a silent study corner, and a general study area. It is important to note that over forty computers are placed in the Computer labs, which provide on-line access to the Internet. The library is open from 9:00 a.m. till 7:00 p.m. on all working days and from 3:00 p.m. to 7:00 p.m. on Fridays.\n\nThere is an exclusive library for BUMS and BAMS students and teachers in the second building. It is also equipped with books, computers, and jonrnals for the Faculty of Unani and Ayurvedic Medicine.</string>

    <string name="admissionRequirement">Application Form, Admission Instructions, Prospectus of the University and other related information are available at the Admission Office on the Hamdard University Campus by paying a fee of Tk. 300.\nCompleted Application must be submitted to the Admission Office within the announced deadline. Admission form and related information are also available and can be downloaded from the University website: www.hamdarduniversity.edu.bd.</string>

    <string name="applicationInclude">1.Completed Application Form.\n2.Two recent passport size color photographs, duly attested.\n3.Attested copies of Certificates and Mark Sheets of all previous Examinations.\n4.Testimonial/ Letter of Recommendation from the Head of the Institution last attended.\n5.Attested copy of National Identity Card/ Birth registration certificate/ Valid Passport.\n</string>

    <string name="undergaduate">For eligibility of admission into an undergraduate program of Hamdard University Bangladesh, a candidate must meet the following requirements:\n1. Minimum GPA of 2.5 in SSC and HSC exams separately. Or O-Level in five subjects and A-Level in two subjects with a GPA of 3 at each level. In case of GPA 2.00 in one of the SSC or HSC Exam, the total GPA will have to be 6.0.\n2.Candidates who have completed higher secondary education (12 years of schooling) under a system different form SSC/ HSC or O/ A levels will be considered for equivalence by the University on a case to case basis.\n3.Candidates for BSc in Mathematics, Computer Science and Engineering (CSE), Electrical and Electronic Engineering (EEE) must have Physics and Mathematics at HSC or A-level.\n4.Candidates for BSc in Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) and BSc in Mathematics must have Mathematics at HSC or A-level.\n5.Candidates with break of study of more than two years will have to apply separately stating a valid cause of break of study.\n6.Candidates for BUMS and BAMS must have Biology and Chemistry at  HSC or A Level.</string>

    <string name="gaduate">For eligibility of admission into a graduate program of Hamdard University Bangladesh, a candidate must meet the following requirements:\n1.A total of 15 years of study in school and college level and at least a bachelor’s degree.\n2.Minimum GPA of 2.5 or second division in SSC, HSC and Bachelor or equivalent degrees.\n3.Alternatively, HSC-Letter grades/ O-Level (in five subjects) and A-Level (in two subjects with a GPA of 2.5 or above).\n4.Candidates with third division or less than CGPA of 2.00 at any level of education are noteligible to apply.</string>

    <string-array name="faculty_array">
        <item>FACULTY MEMBERS</item>
        <item>Faculty of Science, Engineering and Technology</item>
        <item>Faculty of Business Administration</item>
        <item>Faculty of Arts and Social Science</item>
        <item>Faculty of Natural Medicine</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="cafe_text">There is a spacious and well-ventilated cafeteria in the university. It can accommodate up to 100 students at any given time . It serves a variety of snacks,meals and drinks. Cafeteria and tea shops at campus not only provide quality food but also the rendezvous for informal gatherings.</string>
    <string name="transport_text">The University bus service is provided to Students . Seats are available on a first come first served basis. The bus service runs during term time only.</string>
    <string name="hostel_text">Hostel facilities for girls and boys are available near the campus in rented houses within walking distance. Part of the establishment is borne by the University, while students pay for the monthly rent, utilities and food. Since HUB will be a residential institution, the authority is very careful in renting and maintaining the hostel facilities to provide optimum ease and comfort to the students.</string>
    <string name="about_devloper">Md. Abdullah Al Maruf\nDepartment of CSE\nHamdard University Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="about_special_thanks">Md. Ismail Jabiullah\nDean\nFaculty of Science Engineering and Technology\nHead\nDepartment of CSE\nHamdard University Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bus_tracker">Bus Tracker</string>
</resources>
